Our motto is provide a human touch.
Now you know we've been in
the temp business 15 years,
and yes more than once
bankruptcy reared its head.
But I used every dirty trick in the
book to get us back on our feet.
On this fine day I finally get to taste the
fruits of all the blood sweat and tears!
Delicious!
You're safe, Mr. President. No poison.
Bon Appetit!
To Tom Otsu and not Sumi
Congratulations on your marriage.
Make sure you pump out a
bunch of healthy boys for me
Cheers!
Mr.
Brendan, you useless priest.
No, you've got to listen to me.
I'm not telling you I didn't poison him.
So, how'd you pull it off?
Couldn't have been easy slipping
poison past a hotshot taste tester.
The taster ate a lethal dose as
well, he just wasn't aware of it.
I'm confused.
How'd he live?
I spent the past three months adding
minuscule amounts to his food.
Until eventually, he built
up an immunity to the poison.
No offense, but that sounds
absurdly time-consuming Well, yeah,
so absurd no one would think
we'd be crazy enough to try it
The name of the game is stay
one step ahead of everyone else
So, Hikaru, have you given any
thought to the thing we talked about?
What thing?
You getting married
Akari, do you seriously
think I'm cut out for that?
It's not like I meet any women at work
Still...
I know.
Grandma says there's got to be
a new head of the Poison Clan.
Either you or me.
When I tried to tell her
I'm out because I'm single,
she matched me up with a total
stranger from a branch family?
and nearly forced me to get hitched.
As if I'm that desperate to get married.
The Poison Master's line will end with me.
I'm spending my life single.
And you should spend yours
with your girlfriend.
Well, not like I can see
girls going for you anyway.
Jerk.
Bugmaster, been a while.
Glad you could make it.
Julia, cut that out.
Cheers.
Word is the needle
master has three kids now
all of them boys food
bill must be a nightmare.
Me I'm planning on staying a bachelor the
rest of my life easiest
way to keep my sanity.
Yeah about that I haven't told you yet
but I'm getting hitched pretty soon.
She's a nice quiet girl.
And she accepts me for who I
am bugs and all. Seriously?
Caught you off guard, huh?
Honestly, I figured you'd
have more trouble than me.
Man, you wouldn't know the pain,
but I nearly died landing her!
Well, well, look at you turning traitor?
Hey, kiddo.
Rest assured, marriage won't change the
fact that you and I are still best buds.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
Congrats.
See you, ghetto.
Let's do this again when things settle.
Wait, Bugmaster.
Respect, really.
Finding someone you care
about and who cares about you?
I don't think I'll ever
be able to do that.
It's not like I've ever had
a high opinion of marriage.
But after hearing you talk about it tonight
it's crazy but I found myself thinking
that that sounds all right as
if it's ever going to happen for
me though it's such
an honor to have you here man it looks like
the business has been doing pretty well
back thanks to guys like you we offer
cleaning services and
we'll get our hands dirty
for prices so affordable even your average
Joe can swing them oh the ladies work here
they're kind of assassin secretaries very
versatile so feel free to use it for work
pleasure or however you like no thanks no
the ladies don't do it for you oh master
ghetto watch out for i see you're admiring
our bulletproof glass partition up close
meet the latest piece of human scum i'd
like your help with i present the heartless
marriage swindler, Mei Kinosaki.
Girls caused all sorts of trouble
on our turf, but her meddling's
coming to an end right here and right now.
Enjoy. Hello.
And who are you?
Here's what's in store for
you.
The poison will paralyze
nerves in your extremities.
Then, it'll travel towards your
brain and make you feel like
you're being ripped to shreds.
Keep in mind,
you're going to be fully
conscious while it's happening
finally i will conclude with
this coup de grace i concocted.
your last thought will be
regretting you were born?
let's back up i'm mei kinosaki and your
name is what have we met before? shut it.
i i'm sorry but i i asked because
you remind me of my first love.
but alas so now the marriage swindler
is flirting with me to save herself.
Yes, I'll admit it.
I've gotten several people.
But the only reason I did it is
because I desperately needed the money.
My little brother's sick
and needs treatment.
I took all the loans I could get and
work jobs I'd never confess to anyone,
but I still couldn't make enough.
At least I get the chance
to leave this world while
the spinning image of
the man I adored watches.
Maybe I was wrong and
my life isn't so bad.
But before I pass away, at
least tell me your name.
It's Gero.
Are you absolutely sure
about this Gero guy, boss?
He only works on criminal targets
he deems to be human scum.
What kind of game is he playing?
This guy is a legit poison master.
The Geros are one of the oldest
families in the assassination biz.
He might have his fair
share of stupid hang-ups,
but he's the real deal and
comes highly recommended.
So let me sit back and watch him work.
Now what?
I apologize.
Forget I said anything.
The way this woman's acting.
Does she...
Have the hots for me?
I'm sorry to call you
on the emergency line
what's wrong nothing
i'm moving back to the
main house i wanted to
tell you before i go
why there'll be an heir
to the family when i
give birth to a new
poison master one of the
branch members needs a partner too are you
really going to do this
without talking to me
first you don't get it
do you grandma is serious
She told me so herself If you don't
carry on the line and i refuse to
volunteer they'll take away my freedom
and i'll be forced to have children
if that's the alternative
i'd rather go on my own terms
akari Then what are you going
to do about your girlfriend?
Guess we'll have to break up
You can't!
Or else what?
You're going to sacrifice
yourself in my place?
That'll be even worse
This is the only thing I'm good for.
Please, just give me a minute.
If you agree to marry me, I
promise to get you out of here.
The short version is I need to find a partner
to become the head of the Poison Clan.
If I have to be with someone, might
as well be with the girl who likes me.
I can help with your
brother's illness, too.
You can.
Wow, it almost feels unfair
having all of this luck.
My answer is...
There's not a chance in
hell I would marry you.
I wanted to see that face
before I died, guess I am lucky.
If this is how I died, it'd piss me off
going without getting one last shot in.
I'm ready for the void, Hubs!
Whenever you see a couple whether
it's their personalities how much
money they make looks whatever the
reason they're together is because
they make a good match but a piece
of shit who proposes to a target
he can just kill if they say no not
a good match for anyone suppose not
you know i think that
you're gonna have to come
clean with yourself first
that's all you can do
if you're serious about
finding someone people
find their ideal partner
by figuring each other
out butting heads and
running themselves ragged
is that the future you're
after or do you want
to get married for the
inheritance ahem uh master
garrow do you think we
could speed this along
we are paying good money to watch
you do your thing i only dispose of
the human scum that actually deserves
to die nothing to do with justice
i just don't take jobs that'd make
it hard to sleep at night of course
murder is still murder right but
sometimes i'll catch myself wanting
to live a peaceful life with someone
i love and who loves me in return
that side of me makes me sick to
my stomach you want the truth i want
to meet someone i genuinely like
and lead a fun carefree life as much
as the next guy a relationship where
she asks how was your day and we
chat before falling asleep where
she asks are you feeling all right
whenever i cough true love but there's
no way i'll ever meet someone like
that i never went to school not
even daycare i've lived as a poison
master since i was old enough to form
memories showing any sign of weakness
immediately leads to failure i've
never allowed myself to open up to a
stranger like this i've never bared
my heart not until now which means
what are you talking about you
poured your heart out to me and i only
just met you listen you're right
being an assassin is a huge drawback
but i think the solution
is just meeting more
people when you're not
on the clock if you put
yourself out there and
allow your heart to get
broken a time or two I
guarantee that sooner or later,
you'll find your perfect match.
Of course, it'll probably be hell.
That's all I have for
you, so let's finish this.
I've only got myself to
blame for screwing up so bad.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be here and my
brother's medical bills would be paid.
Now I've ruined the future of the
one person I truly care about.
I'm the definition of scum.
Master Ghetto, why don't we call it there?
Yeah, you've heard all the dating
advice our prisoners got to offer.
Now stop delaying and
finish this scumbag off.
I can't.
I require her talents.
Only an expert matchmaker could
have married all those people.
You have what it takes
to find me a partner.
I promise to protect you from
harm, both you and your brother.
In exchange for my help, you'll
find me someone to marry!
You know, I've been in so many
relationships that I've lost count.
But I've never gotten
a proposal like that.
If we...
You can accept it if
you make it out of here.
Gotta say, I'm disappointed, Master Gero.
It's like he said.
So, we have a deal then?
Man, killing the Poison
Master's heir apparent.
We're gonna rocket to the top of
the industry after we take you out.
You people.
You offer your services to
civilians at rock-bottom rates,
then blackmail them the rest
of their lives for hiring you.
How many lives have you ruined?
You think I care? Get real!
What's wrong with conning a few idiots?
Think you're some kind
of hero or something?
I was making sure you meet my condition.
There's no question.
You're all human scum.
Don't stand there!
Let's tease his ass!
Where'd he go? Find him!
You get a front row seat after all.
Now, watch the Poison Master work.
Wow, you were right.
I guess you're not just all talk, huh?
Taking out a room full of
professionals like that?
Zero times anything is still zero.
I only used my 300 torments of hell.
They'll live, but the trauma will
keep them out of the business forever.
Hikaru, what I said earlier, I'm going.
Akari.
You don't have to worry
about succeeding, Grandma.
It's like I said, I don't
have any other choice.
I get it now.
If you're lucky enough to meet someone
you can love and build a life with,
it's the closest thing
to a miracle there is.
What I'm saying is stay
with your girlfriend.
Pass a message on to Grandma.
Tell her that I'm getting married
and leading the Poison Clan.
Just one catch.
No one gets to decide who
my partner is except me.
Got that?
Wait, so are you being serious?
You always decide everything on your own.
I'll go ahead and let her know.
See you soon. Bye.
What's the holdup?
I'm going to need a hand here.
Just how do I carry you?
I've never had to pick up a living girl.
So where should I grab you?
I don't think you'll have to worry
about that, because I'm not a girl.
Oh, great.
Well, in that case...
Wait.
After a bloodbath, a
shower hits different.
How about it, Kero?
Care to join? No thanks.
What's wrong? Afraid?
I said no!
Don't know about you, but
I feel like a new man.
Hilarious.
Bet you're thinking I don't
look like any man you've seen.
You're a professional.
Want to confirm?
What's your deal?
How come you dress in women's clothing?
Easy.
Because my latest mark was a man.
If I needed to dupe a
woman, I'd dress as a guy.
Plus, it's more fun playing both sides.
That was the best move
you could have made.
Proposing to me, I mean. Hang on!
I can teach you to make anyone
fall for you, regardless of gender.
Hurry up and do it!
Step one.
Here, I registered you
for a matchmaking party.
Complete your profile and boom.
Wait, it's after midnight,
which means the event's today.
Profession? No.
Writing the truth is probably a bad idea.
So, self-employed.
There's gonna be way more
men there than women.
I'll captivate the gents with my charms.
That way, there'll be
fewer rivals for you.
Remember, grooming and
fashion only goes so far.
All they do is make a
good first impression.
Leveling them up might get you the
nice guy status, but we want more.
No one's going to fall for you unless
we find your charm and let it shine.
Try different approaches
and see what sticks.
Hi there, it's very nice to meet you.
My research indicates first
impressions are everything,
so I've developed the perfect pickup line.
I'm Gero.
I make million a year
my charm is my income
isn't it says right
here money's desirable?
Yeah maybe so but blabbing
about it right out
of the gate makes it sound
like you're bragging!
This next girl gaze into her eyes and
smile before you open your dumb mouth.
Maybe I'll research how normal
people smile when I get home.
Kero, looky here.
A dating app will give you a chance to
get your bearings when talking to girls.
And good news, I got
you matched right away.
You'll have a ton of chances with this.
You good?
A poison master should never eat
anything someone else serves him.
It's the only way to protect himself.
But I doubt anyone's after
my life this second, right?
Right I'm sure it will be safe.
See I'm doing totally fine.
I'm doing great.
Okay on to the next girl and
the next one and the next?
Impressive.
Over the course of today,
I've met nearly 30 women,
and somehow I didn't exchange
contact info with even one.
You did your best, so don't go
beating yourself up over it.
Our goal is to find your charm.
But while we're working hard
to figure out what that is,
it would have been kind of nice if at
least one date had gone moderately okay.
Kinosaki, have you entertained the
idea of maybe I don't have any charm?
Don't say that.
I know you do.
It's just hidden, so we
can't see what it is yet.
I promise we'll find
someone who's into you.
It seems bleak, but I promise after
I'm finished polishing you up,
some lucky lady is going to
realize that you're the one.
And after watching you, I found
one thing we can work with.
Please tell me.
DIY candy kits.
People with niche hobbies can have
a great time chatting about them.
Also, is it just me or is
this cleaner wicked strong?
It's a mixture I came
up with called Joker.
Using deadly poison to combat stubborn
stains is my favorite way to de-stress.
I can make cleaning agents strong enough
to melt iron when I set my mind to it.
Oh, does this count as
another niche hobby?
Let's just keep that a secret between us.
There you are.
I'm this way.
Guess this is goodnight.
Until tomorrow.
Sure.
Wait, you're putting me
through more torture tomorrow?
So soon?
Hey, Kinosaki.
Want to tell me what you
did to my big brother?
Huh?
Spare me the dumb blonde act.
He said he was going to shake
up this lame-ass industry.
Never could shut up about his big plans,
making those old farts beg for mercy.
Now he wants to take over our
parents' dry-cleaning service.
Maybe he just got tired
of life in the big city?
These are white pellets, though.
That's the kind of look
that gets my blood pumping.
You're going to tell me
everything that went down.
And if you beg for your life
like you mean it, who knows?
I might give you a no - I'd rather die
than team up with trash that con civilians.
You're human scum!
You've got some guts, huh?
You take advantage of
folks the same way we do.
I hate criminals with half-assed morality.
If you can't see a crime as a
crime regardless of the target,
you're not cut out for
this line of work, honey.
That pretty face is the
best weapon you've got,
and I'm gonna make sure
you never use it again.
This next shot will be a shotgun blast.
Hey, boss!
There!
It's Gato.
I see him! Floor it!
Oh, my God.
Taking over the dry cleaning
biz doesn't sound so bad.
You dropped this.
My phone.
I wanted to thank you, Kinosaki.
There's no way I could
have met so many women
in one day without your
guidance and support.
A single rejection would have left me
broken up and moping for a lifetime.
I'm hopeless on my own.
You're all I've got.
I didn't get anyone's info either.
We both struck out.
I'm talking here!
Hey, how would you feel
about trading yours with me?
I doubt my friends list
will get any longer.
Don't know why.
Because you're dazzling me right now.
Wait, that's it.
I found it.
I think I discovered your charm.
This is the story of the elite assassin,
Poison Master Gero Hikaru,
and his search for a bride.
Today, you're going on your first dates.
For her so.
What will you say to her?
With the intent to marry?
Don't you dare.
Next time, what is charm anyway?